{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "email": "test@example.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$7FAKbQ8qDcSMCK03nrcSve646KlblVU50/n/fWhJBs0WihkGnlU8y"
    }
  ],
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": "1752129338693",
      "question": "Kot",
      "answer": "Cat",
      "category": "Zwierzęta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752140116030",
      "question": "Pies",
      "answer": "Dog",
      "category": "Zwierzęta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752142957036",
      "question": "12",
      "answer": "12",
      "category": "12",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752146344297",
      "question": "Krab",
      "answer": "Crab",
      "category": "Zwierzęta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752154627601",
      "question": "Pociąg",
      "answer": "Train",
      "category": "Pojazdy",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752584211866",
      "question": "Ada",
      "answer": "ada",
      "category": "dada",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752679433343",
      "question": "Kot",
      "answer": "Cat",
      "category": "Zwierzęta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752679790279",
      "question": "123",
      "answer": "213",
      "category": "123",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "German"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752679925955",
      "question": "1231",
      "answer": "231",
      "category": "23",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "German"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752680066228",
      "question": "12",
      "answer": "12",
      "category": "12",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "German"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752680247388",
      "question": "21312",
      "answer": "213123",
      "category": "21312",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "German"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752680274988",
      "question": "13",
      "answer": "2132",
      "category": "123",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752680387888",
      "question": "213",
      "answer": "213",
      "category": "123",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752681506992",
      "question": "pies",
      "answer": "dog",
      "category": "zwierzeta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752681834761",
      "question": "Koń morski",
      "answer": "Sea Horse",
      "category": "Zwierzęta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752682002072",
      "question": "123",
      "answer": "123",
      "category": "123",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752682357287",
      "question": "Kot",
      "answer": "Cat",
      "category": "Zwierzeta",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": "1752682424628",
      "question": "Kot",
      "answer": "Cat",
      "category": "123",
      "sourceLang": "Polish",
      "targetLang": "German"
    }
  ]
}